var gameQuestions = [
	{ 
		question: "What's the capital city of Thailand?",
		choice1: "Bangkok",
		choice2: "Hanoi",
		choice3: "Jakarta",
		choice4: "Tokyo",
		correctAns: "Bangkok",
	},
	{ 
		question: "Which country does not have its land on the island of Borneo?",
		choice1: "Brunei",
		choice2: "Malaysia",
		choice3: "Indonesia",
		choice4: "The Philippines",
		correctAns: "The Philippines",
	},

	{ 
		question: "Which country is a landlock country?",
		choice1: "Vietnam",
		choice2: "Cambodia",
		choice3: "Laos",
		choice4: "Myanmar",
		correctAns: "Laos",
	},

	{ 
		question: "Which country has the largest population in Southeast Asia?",
		choice1: "Singapore",
		choice2: "Thailand",
		choice3: "Indonesia",
		choice4: "The Philippines",
		correctAns: "Indonesia",
	},

	{ 
		question: "Angkor Wat is located in....",
		choice1: "Brunei",
		choice2: "Myanmar",
		choice3: "Indonesia",
		choice4: "Cambodia",
		correctAns: "Cambodia",
	},

	{ 
		question: "What's the currency of Malaysia?",
		choice1: "Kip",
		choice2: "Ringit",
		choice3: "Rupee",
		choice4: "Baht",
		correctAns: "Ringit",
	},

	{ 
		question: "Which country was colonized by the Dutch for over 300 years?",
		choice1: "Singapore",
		choice2: "The Philippines",
		choice3: "Indonesia",
		choice4: "Cambodia",
		correctAns: "Indonesia",
	},

	{ 
		question: "Hibiscus is the national flower of.....",
		choice1: "Malaysia",
		choice2: "Thailand",
		choice3: "Laos",
		choice4: "Myanmar",
		correctAns: "Malaysia",
	},

	{ 
		question: "Which of these countries was not colonized by the British?",
		choice1: "Singapore",
		choice2: "Vietnam",
		choice3: "Malaysia",
		choice4: "Myanmar",
		correctAns: "Vietnam",
	},

	{ 
		question: "Timor Leste is the newest country in Southeast Asia. Which country did it seperate from?",
		choice1: "Indonesia",
		choice2: "Singapore",
		choice3: "Malaysia",
		choice4: "Myanmar",
		correctAns: "Indonesia",
	},

]